Please call Stella.
Ask her to bring these things with her from the store.
Six spoons of fresh snow peas, five thick slabs of blue cheese, and maybe a snack for her brother Bob.
We also need a small plastic snake and a big toy frog for the kids.
She can scoop these things into three red bags, and we will go meet her Wednesday at the train station.
When the sunlight strikes raindrops in the air, they act as a prism and form a rainbow.
The rainbow is a division of white light into many beautiful colors.
These take the shape of a long round arch, with its paths high above, and its two ends apparently beyond the horizon.
There is , according to legend, a boiling pot of gold at one end.
People look, but no one ever finds it.
When a man looks for something beyond his reach, his friends say he is looking for the pot of gold at the end of the rainbow.
Throughout the centuries people have explained the rainbow in various ways.
Some have accepted it as a miracle without physical explanation.
To the Hebrews it was a token that there would be no more universal floods.
The Greeks used to imagine that it was a sign from the gods to foretell war or heavy rain.
