And so, howsoever reluctantly, she had gone.
"What's the mere color of a human soul's skin," she had cried to a Wellesley audience and the audience had applauded with enthusiasm.
But here in Alabama, brought closely and intimately in touch with these dark skinned children, their color struck her at first with a sort of terror-it seemed ominous and forbidding.
She groped for new ways to teach colored brains and marshal colored thoughts and the result was puzzling both to teacher and student.
Miss Smith represented the older New England of her parents-honest, inscrutable, determined, with a conscience which she worshipped, and utterly unselfish.
She appealed to Miss Taylor's ruddier and daintier vision but dimly and distantly as some memory of the past.
The other teachers were indistinct personalities, always very busy and very tired, and talking "school room" with their meals.
Miss Taylor was soon starving for human companionship, for the lighter touches of life and some of its warmth and laughter.
She wanted a glance of the new books and periodicals and talk of great philanthropies and reforms.
She felt out of the world, shut in and mentally anaemic; great as the "Negro Problem" might be as a world problem, it looked sordid and small at close range.
So for the hundredth time she was thinking today, as she walked alone up the lane back of the barn, and then slowly down through the bottoms.
She paused.
The glimmering sea of delicate leaves whispered and murmured before her, stretching away to the Northward. She remembered that beyond this little world it stretched on and on-how far she did not know-but on and on in a great trembling sea, and the foam of its mighty waters would one time flood the ends of the earth.
She glanced absently at the boys.
Then her New England conscience stepped in.
